Finding Aid for Campus Information Centers (University of Michigan) records, 1983-[Ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Campus Information Centers (University of Michigan) records 1983-[Ongoing] 1988-1990
University of Michigan. Campus Information Centers.
4 linear ft.
9936 Bimu B6 2
The Campus Information Centers publications include miscellaneous brochures and manuals created by the Campus Information Centers and calendars and flyers collected by the CIC from various campus units describing activities and events held on the campus.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records of the Campus Information Centers (Donor no. 7319 ) were first received in 1986; additional accessions are received on a periodic basis.
The collection is open to research.
The Campus Information Centers were established as part of the renovation of the Michigan Union. A proposal for an information center was written in 1978, and after two years of deliberation the CIC desk opened in the Michigan Union in 1980. The second CIC desk opened in Pierpont Commons on North Campus in 1990. In addition to the information desks, CIC serves the campus community by maintaining the University's electronic events calendar, UM*Events (http://events.umich.edu), answering questions through email and telephone requests, and posting information at their website (http://www.umich.edu/~info/).
The mission of CIC is to fulfill the needs of University of Michigan students, staff, faculty, alumni, prospective students, and visitors by providing accurate and timely information, in a central location, about campus resources, services and events. CIC is a sub-department of the University of Michigan Technology Services which in turn is a branch of Department of Student Affairs
The Campus Information Centers publications collection contains one series of Printed Materials which includes the three subseries of Brochures, Calendars and Flyers, and Manuals. The brochures were created by the Campus Information Centers on general topics such as "Campus Walking Tours" and "Accomodations" at the University of Michigan. The Calendars and Flyers were collected by CIC from various campus departments, and the subseries also contains a small amount of correspondence. The Manuals subseries contains several manuals intended to orient new students to campus and local area resources.
Subjects:
Korn, Harold A. (Harold Allen); University of Michigan.; Videotapes.
- Printed Materials
  - Brochures, 1986-1990 (Box 1)
  - Calendars and Flyers
    - September-December 1987, 6 folders (Box 1)
    - January-December 1988, 21 folders (Box 1)
    - January-December 1989, 34 folders (Box 2)
    - January-December 1990, 38 folders (Box 3)
    - January-May 1991, 7 folders (Box 3)
    - January-July 1992, 12 folders (Box 3)
    - August-December 1992, 19 folders (Box 4)
    - January-April 1993, 6 folders (Box 4)
  - Manuals
    - Resource Guide for New Students, 1983-1986 (Box 4)
Related Materials
Also of interest to researchers is a video cassette entitled: Compilation of UM Institutional Messages and segment from CBS Morning News including a brief interview with Harold Korn. The video is in the Campus Information Centers visual material collection.